TheDarkMaster[TDM] -=MTR=-
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is your captain speaking.
Hope you 're well rested.
ln about five minutes,
we will be beginning our descent
into New Delhi lnternational airport -
- on to runway 4R.
Weather on the ground
is a cool fifteen degrees Celsius.
There's a slight haze
and a little bit of turbulence,
so please keep your seatbelts fastened.
Excuse me, is this seat taken?
Vladimir, right?
Hi, when did you get here?
Sit down!
Please, act like you don't know me.
l don't know you .
Don't look at me.
Oh.
So, how was your flight?
Don't talk to me -
- just do as you were told.
God. Fucking mental, some people.
Open the door!
l got it last time.
Arup! Open the fucking door!
He's lying! l got it last time.
Bastard, one more time l'll cut
your balls off and make you earrings.
All right fucker, you 're dead.
You deaf?
When did you get back?
Just now.
Oh my gosh.
Tashi, you 're scratching me.
Please go shave.
Can't.
There's no water.
What do you mean, there's no water?
You get two hours of water every morning.
Yeah, we forgot to put the buckets out.
What do you mean,
forgot to put the buckets out?
Him.
What?
lt was his turn.
Yeah, but you could hear
the water running, right?
All you had to do was get out of bed
and put the buckets out.
lt would have taken you all of thirty seconds.
Yeah. But it was his turn.
Oh my god! l can't believe
you guys live like this.
What are you getting so worked up for?
We'll do it tomorrow.
Because you 're meeting my parents for lunch.
l want you to shave and look presentable.
l'm meeting your parents?
Wear this.
l've told you not to buy me
such expensive stuff.
Just wear it, Tashi.
People judge you by the way you look.
Yeah, l don't hang out with
any of those people.
Listen, l'm not joking, okay Tashi?
You have no idea how pissed l am.
l'm going home now. Don't be late.
Oh, man -
Baby, can you drop this for me, please?
- This afternoon? lt's urgent.
- l have an assignment, can't...
Here's the address.
That girl really loves you .
Lucky bastard.
So, where is she?
l'm looking.
Why? You don't know
what she looks like.
Shut up.
You have her number?
No.
Man, you 're the cow
on the information superhighway.
Me? You 're the one
still shooting film, you choot.
Digital is for fucking tourists.
You 're ringing,
so you must be Tashi.
Hi, l'm Menaka.
Hey, hi, Tashi.
A couple more hours and
we would've found you .
This is Nitin, my photographer.
Menaka's a special correspondent,
just started with us today.
Hi, Special Correspondent.
Welcome.
Alright, shall we?
Because l want to do everything l can,
you know. No limits.
How would you define everything?
Singing. Acting.
l think, directing. No wait.
Definitely directing.
l paint.
l'm working on
my first collection of poems.
And l want to have my very own
clothes line one day.
Clothing line.
What?
Never mind.
So, what do you enjoy most,
out of everything that you do?
Everything.
Of course. Just everything.
That's why she does it all.
Just -
Lovely.
Could you sing us one of your songs?
Oh, l don't know.
Come on, we've only got
a couple of minutes, come on.
- Okay.
- Brilliant.
Okay, it's called -
l hate you , like l love you .
Like l love you in brackets.
So, it's like, l hate you ,
brackets, like l love you .
l hate you , like l love you ,
in brackets. That's brilliant.
I hate you ,
IIke I Iove you ,
IIke I Iove you .
And then the drums come in.
That's it.
Are those your lyrics?
Yeah -
We shouldn't have
asked you to sing -
- l can't get it
out of my head now.
So true.
Hey, do you want me to
sign something for you ?
Because l don't mind.
Really? That's -
You know how some celebrities
get all high and mighty?
l just don't get it.
Waste of my time.
Hey, that's priceless.
From this moment on,
any time you 're depressed -
- l want you to
take a look at this and say -
- l hate you , like l love you ,
in brackets.
lt's a magic photo.
You can have it.
Tuneless and brainless.
Hey man, being hot is like
a full time job.
Dude, there's real news to be covered,
and this is the crap l get?
Listen, she was news to me, okay?
And honestly, l'd
be happy to cover her anytime.
With what, your paunch?
For starters.
You met my friend Nitin,
the serial rapist?
Hello, serial rapist.
Did you get something?
Yeah, some for you ,
some for me.
All right, l'll be back
after lunch.
Menaka, nice to meet you .
Where did l leave that package?
- Hey!
- Oh.
- That's mine!
- Sorry.
HeIIo, Arup?
Arup?
Can you hear me?
What, fucker?
Oh, no, no -
l was on the phone.
Arup?
Hold on bastard.
Okay Arup, this is nice.
Very nIce.
Thanks.
But do you think you can
make him a little happier?
Happier? Who, the banana?
Haan, you know like
he's having fun.
All his life he's wanted to
be in a banana-split -
- and this is like a dream come true.
Dream come true, for the banana?
You know happy, something like -
Could you just - one more?
lf that's all right -
You got it?
First thing tomorrow, l'll -
No, no, no, now, the client is waiting -
Right now?
Drop everything else -
do it now.
HeIIo, Arup?
Arup, you there?
- What?
Hey, I need a favour,
can you drop that package off for me?
No, l can't.
Didn't you hear that?
l'm stuck in fucking banana hell.
- And she wanted to touch a kIIIer whaIe.
- Come on they are IIke doIphIns.
Amma?
Papa? What are you doIng here?
Surprise!
Even my mama's daughter got married
on the 29th of November -
- and they're so happy Mrs. Lhatoo!
Sorry, 29th November?
That's just a month away.
You don't have to worry,
Your mother and l will do
all the running around.
lsn't that true, Mrs. Lhatoo?
That's what mothers do, beta.
lt's one.
Where's that driver, mummy?
Wasn't he supposed to
be here at one?
l have to go the tailor's after this.
Relax, he'll be here.
Tashi, did you drop that stuff?
Hello? Yeah, Menaka -
- yeah?
Yeah, l know where it is.
Yeah, l'll tell Nitin -
- Okay, bye.
Uncle, Aunty - l'm really sorry, l've have
to go, something's come up at work.
No more uncle-aunty.
Beta, you 're family now.
From now on, mummy-daddy.
What do you say, Mr. Lhatoo?
That's how it is.
Tashi, beta, come with me, beta.
l should really get going, Daddy -
Tashi, come, come.
This will take hardly one minute. Come on -
You IIke It?
Good. Take it. lt's for you .
Oh, l can't, Daddy -
Forget it. We're not even discussing it.
Bachche, we've even bought a flat for you .
Just five minutes away.
ln the morning we'll walk over
to your place for breakfast
and in the evening
you 'll both come over for dinner.
lt'll be wonderful. l just can't wait.
Delicate.
You can work wonders with the right model.
l'm guessing this is some for you -
- and some for me.
Bacche, say cheese.
Man, is nothing sacred?
He doesn't mind. l asked him.
So that pretty young thing
was a waste of your time
and this is worthwhile?
l don't know what that says about you .
That he's a serious journalist.
Yeah. Or a necrophiliac.
Yeah, a gay necrophiliac.
Fucking idiots.
Yours.
Mine.
- You 're not coming in?
- No. Work to do.
Listen, l got to file this.
Can you drop this off for me?
No.
Thanks.
Here's the address.
Go.
What are you doing this evening?
Oh, you know.
Work.
All work, no play, Tashi...
dull boy.
Give me one.
Make it spicy!
Let me go.
You want some of this?
200? Rate's gone up.
No, my darling.
Asshole.
Hi.
Oh fuck!
What are you doing,
lying in the dark like that?
l'm sick, man.
l feel poisoned.
Did you see a doctor?
Yeah.
So here's what you need to do.
Just take my scooter.
Why?
Just take it.
Fucker!
Why am l taking your scooter?
Tashi asked me to
drop off this package.
That fucking thing is
still floating around?
Listen if l wasn't sick,
l'd do it.
Sure.
Listen, since you 're
going out in any case,
can you do me a favour?
What?
Bastards!
Bastards.!
This world is full of uncivilized people.
Don't pay them any attention.
Again? From the top?
So, the doctor has to
check for food poisoning.
Good.
Do you mind - l have to
send him a stool sample?
Fuck off.
Patient name?
Nitin Berry.
Mr. Bhatia...
Okay, l'll talk to you later.
Sir...
this is shit.
Thank you .
Sisterfucker.
New car?
Yes.
Very nice! Beauty, great colour.
Thank you , Mr. Jain.
Mr. Tashi, l just wanted to remind you
that the rent is due next week.
l know, Mr. Jain.
Good. Good. Very good.
lt is just that it was
late last month -
- and the month before
that also, that's why.
You said you 'll speak to
Mr. Maharaj about the dancing.
Every night bharatnatyam
on our heads.
Kathak.
See, l spoke to him -
- and he said that he will try
and take his class early.
That was last week.
Really?
Hi.
What's wrong with you ?
Bastard, l'm dying.
Okay. And you ?
Meeting Ritu for a movie.
''Return of Disco Fighter''
Where are my pants?
Okay, just hang on a second -
something l want to talk to you about.
Two things.
l don't know about that Ritu .
That girl, she doesn't
give me a good feeling.
Yeah, she's my girlfriend -
- only supposed to
give me a good feeling.
You 're my witness.
l warned him.
Listen, rent's due next week.
- l'd like to pay it on time this month.
- Sure.
Nitin?
Yeah, l'm not paying rent anymore.
ldiot.
You 're moving out?
No.
You 're not moving out and
you 're not going to pay rent.
How the fuck are you
going to manage that?
Check this out.
What the hell is this?
lt's a naked man lying
on top of a naked woman -
- it's called fucking.
This is Manish, our landlord.
Yeah, the fucking wife-cheater.
And that's Leena.
She's a whore.
No.
l thought she was sucking his dick
because she's really outgoing -
- but a whore you say, my God.
Bastard, if l wasn't sick,
l'd fucking give you one.
How'd you get these?
No, that's the wrong question.
The right question is,
are we going to pay rent anymore?
And the answer is?
No. No more rent.
No more fucking rent.
What are you talking about?
l'm talking about a small
business transaction with our landlord.
He gives us some money and
these pictures don't get to his wife.
You 're going to blackmail him?
lt's not blackmail.
lt's a sign, from God.
Oh, you 're going to blackmail him.
We're living with a criminal.
lt's Nitin Sobhraj.
l'm just the higher moral authority
in Manish's life -
You 're the higher moral authority
in his life?
Yes, yes, and l'm asking
him to mend his evil ways -
- l'm not a benevolent god.
Don't tell me anymore, right -
- because when the cops
come to get you ,
l don't want to be dragged in
as an accessory.
An accessory?
Listen to him using big words.
An earring is an accessory, you choot -
- listen l've been in this business
for two years, nobody gets -
l'm sorry, you 've been in this
business for two years?
Listen, l do all the work -
- you fuckers get to save rent money.
Everybody wins.
And two?
Two? l'm getting married.
Yeah, we know that.
No, getting married next month.
Really, l thought this wasn't happening
till like next year.
Yeah, but then l thought, what difference?
Sooner the better.
Right up till the moment
they chop his head off,
the goat thinks he's going for a walk
in the park.
Bastard, you 're just too negative.
l hate this attitude.
Listen, this is great news.
Come here, give me a hug.
Great news!
Fucker, l was looking for these -
- your ass is like a solar eclipse, man.
Listen she's too hot, l was going to
marry her myself, but you can have her.
She's too sexy, you lucky bastard!
He's moving out.
You 're moving out?
Then why the fuck were you
going on about the rent?
Tashi, you really should shave, baby.
HeIIo? Menaka? Yes -
Tashi? Tashi, get back in there!
l know where it is -
Okay, should l bring Nitin?
l can't believe you !
- Okay, bye.
- Oh, my God, this guy.
Fucking buffoon.
Baby, l've got to go
Look, it's work, l swear
l'll make it up to you , okay?
Just go, Tashi, just go.
Thank you .
Do you see her, right behind me?
Don't look, don't look.
What about her?
That's Kanika Tuli.
l heard she's a lesbo.
Really? Where'd you hear that?
Oh, you know, here and there.
Considering some of the men
l've been with, that doesn't sound half bad.
Oh, come on, don't tell me you 've never
thought about being with a woman.
No! Never!
So, did you see Rajeev yet?
l think he's around.
Nope.
Excuse me.
Sure.
Do you see her? Don't look.
That's Menaka Vashisht.
She's a lesbo.
Really?
So, what's the story?
Story?
Yeah, you know, you called me, gave me
the address, told me to come over -
Yeah, l know - l'm not that drunk. Yet.
l didn't say anything about a story,
l just gave you the address.
So l came here for nothing?
No, to have a drink, have some fun.
Tashi, stop working.
l was in the middle of something -
Couldn't have been that important.
What?
Why'd you pick up the phone then?
l'm glad you 're having fun -
- l'll talk to you tomorrow.
When you 're sober.
Tash, come on.
Lover's spat?
Rajeev, l'm not in the mood
for your bullshit, okay?
So why don't you just leave?
Make me.
Listen, man - l don't know you , okay?
Do you mind?
Yeah. l mind.
What the fuck?
What's your problem, man?
What did you just say?
What the fuck?
- Come on, say it again!
- Guys!
Say it again, come on.
Listen, man, l'm not
looking for trouble, alright?
No, bitch,
trouble's looking for you .
- Should've kept your mouth shut!
- Leave me alone, you bastard!
- Now mind your fucking business!
- You bastard!
- Come here, you , come here -
- You fucking bastard!
You think you can
get away with this -
- nobody messes with
Rajeev Khanna and gets -
Let's go - he has friends.
Fucker.!
- Are you all right?
- l'm fine.
Let me see that -
- that doesn't look so good.
l'm fine.
l'm really sorry.
l just wanted you to loosen up,
have a good time -
lt's okay.
What do you mean, loosen up?
No, l didn't mean it like that -
l am loose, okay?
With friends, people who know me -
- people who don't feel the need to
drag me half-way across the city -
- in the middle of the fucking night,
so l can loosen up.
Don't be an asshole.
l apologized.
l was just trying to be nice.
- Where should l drop you off?
- Just - wherever.
Fuck!
Can't believe this guy!
Hey - hey bastard!
l'll fucking kill you , you bastard!
Tashi, go, go, go!
Son of a bItch.!
l'll fucking kill you !
Go, go, go, go. Fuck.
l'm going to fucking shoot
you like a dog!
l'll kill you , you bitch!
What's wrong with that crazy fuck?
- you bitch, you 're done!
Fuck, okay -
Asshole!
Bloody hell!
l'll fucking kill you !
Fuck you !
Fuck.
Hang on.
Stop, sisterfucker!
l'll kill you , you bastard!
Get after him!
Fuck, where the fuck do we go?
Park it!
Bastard.!
Come on, come on -
Come on, quick!
There he is!
Stop, motherfucker.!
Stop - stop, you bastard!
- But which one?
- Fuck it, let's go!
That's fine, that's fine.
Don't worry about it.
Okay, ma'am.
- Bathroom? ls it done?
- Yes ma'am. Thank you , ma'am.
Thank you .
Thank you , sir.
Fuck, my car.
My brand new car.
Who's the asshole?
My husband.
Ex-husband, as soon as
the divorce papers show up.
l can't believe he took a shot at me.
Where'd you find him?
Oh, you know. Arranged marriage.
Parents forced me.
Really?
No. He was my boyfriend in school -
- l actually ran away from
home to marry him.
l fought with my parents.
You know how to pick them.
Sitting here with you .
l'm going to get some coffee.
You want some?
You can't just do that. That's not -
Anyone who can afford to stay
at this hotel,
can afford to buy us a cup of coffee -
Cappuccino okay?
What, you do this on a regular basis?
No, just on days
l get shot at by my ex-husband -
- hi, l'm calling from room 509 -
- can you please send up
two cappuccinos?
Hold on.
Would you like something to eat?
No, just the coffees, thank you .
This is wrong.
You need to fucking lighten up.
Fuck it - let's go, come.
Yes, baby!
Just a little harder!
Excuse us!
Oh my god! Yes, yes!
Fuck me, fuck me, fuck me.!
Yes, yes, yes!
Like a horse!
ln the back!
In the back, In the back.!
Spank me bItch, spank me -
- IIke a horse.!
In the back.!
More, more, in the back! Come on -
- come on.!
l could've sworn that was our room.
Frank, l hope this isn't Alzheimer's.
Louise, the key worked!
Mr. and Mrs. Eggen,
l have your coffee.
We didn't order any coffee.
Thanks for the lift.
And l'd be happy to
pay for your window.
lt's all right.
You didn't shoot it.
'Night.
Did you put the buckets out?
Bastard, l'm dying.
Man, did you drink all my juice?
Yeah.
There were like
3-4 cartons in there.
l know.
You don't even like orange juice.
Sometimes l do.
Man -
l'll buy you some more.
Damn right you 'll buy me some more -
Did you wash your ass
with my juice?
Bastard, l told you
l'll buy you some more -
- my fucking ass cheeks are
stuck together.
l can never drink orange juice again.
Yes, Mum -
- yes, how many times are you
going to tell me the same thing?
Okay, Mum, and listen,
please do not forget to pick up
my lehenga from the designer.
l just know that guy,
he will not be done on time.
Yes.
Yeah, Mum. Okay, okay, bye.
Love you , bye.
Hey, baby -
What?
What happened to you ?
Work.
Work?
Work? They don't pay you
enough to get killed.
My dad gives you a brand new car -
- and this is what you do to it, Tashi?
You 're going to miss your flight.
- This is it?
- Yes.
Who is it?
Sir, laundry.
No, thanks.
Laundry?
You idiot.
Move.
Hold on.
Yes, sir?
Which room is this for?
50 7, sir.
l'll take it.
No, sir, l can't do that.
l have to deliver the food myself.
See, he's my friend.
lt's his birthday, we want to surprise him.
Yes sir, l understand, sir -
but - it's hotel -
- policy -
R. Balachander.
lf there's a problem, l'll talk to your manager.
But, sir -
Here, buy something for the kids.
Sir, l'm not married.
For yourself then?
No, sir. l can't do that, sir.
l have to deliver the food myself,
for reasons of quality.
You have to deliver it?
Yes, sir.
For the reasons of quality?
Take it.
Ready, sir?
Who is it?
Room service. Sir, your lunch.
Yeah, you can come in.
And happy birthday, sir.
Sorry, but it's not my birthday.
What the fuck?
Surprise.
Yeah, what are you doing here?
Delivering your food, man.
Unlike you , we make our deliveries.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Bunty.
Hey, easy!
This was a new shirt, man.
- Even dry-cleaning won't get that out.
- Balls.
Just got it from the tailor yesterday.
Where is my package?
l sent it, like every time.
But l didn't get it.
So, where is it?
l brought it in -
- and gave it to the courier,
like every time!
There was this new girl.
New girl?
Yeah -
- my regular girl was sick, so -
- she told me her friend
could help us -
- could help us out, for free.
Only this time.
The new girl didn't know
what she was carrying.
She didn't know!
Yeah -
- l'm sure.
Search the room.
Sisterfuckers, what is this, a wedding?
This is very nice, Arup.
Very nice.
The client also liked it very much.
Only thing, they felt that
the banana is smiling too much.
Too happy.
Why? He's about to get eaten -
- what could be wrong?
You want me to make him sad?
Yes, not too much.
About seven percent.
Anything for me?
No, nothing.
l'm going to take a bath.
You just took a bath.
lt's really hot. l'm really hot.
l feel like taking a bath again.
Are you done?
No, no.
Mr. Tashi!
Mr. Ni -
Nitin?
Nothing.
l swear l don't have it.
You got to believe me now.
This girl she - she must've messed up.
Give me her number.
What?
Her phone number.
lt's - 986 -
- 7, 6, 6 -
No - 7, 6, 5 -
- 1 , 9, 9, 0.
Gupta Stationary Mart. Hello?
No, no, l must've mixed it up, l mean -
Bunty.
No, l -
- don't!
No, no -
Why should l be here
if l want to cheat you ?
Because you don't know me.
What's that?
lt is something to clear your brain, man.
What are you doing?
Number.
Number?
9, 8, 7 - no, 6 -
- 7, 6, 5 -
1 , 6 -
- fuck!
Number is 6 -
1 , 9, 9, 0 - no!
1 ,9 - 1 , 1 , 9, 0. 1 , 1 , 9, 0!
Please! Put it off, please!
Get it off!
HeIIo, you 've reached SonIya.
Please, put it out!
PIease Ieave a message after the beep. Bye.
Sorry.
Leave her a message - call back urgently.
And now, l'm calling her again -
- this time, leave a proper
message, okay?
Yeah.
And also, call the room service,
order some food -
- what do you idiots want to eat?
Hey.
What happened,
where were you yesterday?
Arup, what are you doing here?
Who Is It?
No one, Mum.
Arup, you shouldn't be here.
What's going on?
Hey, guys -
- your friend?
Yeah, a friend.
Ritu 's friends are my friends.
Arup, this is Vivek -
- he's a computer engineer in Canada.
Hey, nice to meet you , dude -
- l hope you 're coming for the wedding.
Wedding?
He doesn't know?
l was just about to tell him -
- actually, Arup's here to pick up his stuff -
- he's a cartoonist.
l'll be back.
A cartoonist?
Like - like Chacha Choudhry?
Yeah, like Chacha Choudhry.
That's, that's funny.
Vivek, your tea is getting cold.
All right, yeah -
- hey, good to see you , dude.
Hey -
- old jungle saying -
- phantom fist is quicker than the eye.
See you at the wedding.
When were you planning to tell me?
Arup, it doesn't matter -
- in a month, l'm moving to Canada.
Your tea Is gettIng coId.
You should go now, Arup. Please.
Good luck with your cartooning.
The bride and groom
may now exchange garlands.
Stop!
This marriage cannot happen!
This girl has given me blowjob.
Blowjob.
And because l am 21 st century man,
l have given her oral pleasure also.
Oh my God! Are you alright?
Shameless girl!
You 've disgraced the family name!
Get out of my sight!
You have two voice messages.
HI SonIya, It's VIadImIr -
- I want you to caII back
as soon as possIbIe -
It's very urgent, so If you can do that -
thank you very much.
Hello?
Hello, Vladimir, it's Soniya,
l got your message.
Good, good, good -
- l want to ask you about the package
you have to deliver -
- did you deliver it?
You know, actually, l didn't -
but l gave it to a friend to deliver -
- l had to do some shopping
before the flight.
Are you crazy?
After l told exactly what to do -
- you think this is a joke?
You think this is a picnic -
- that we are on a picnic?
You are so fucking stupid!
God.
Hello?
Well done.
HeIIo, you 've reached SonIya.
PIease Ieave me a message
after the beep, bye.
Vladimir.
Hello, yes?
Hello, Miss Soniya?
Now who's this?
Hi, Miss Soniya, this is Vladimir's supervisor -
- l'm calling to say sorry for his behaviour.
He's a very rude man, okay? Very rude -
- l only did this as a favour to him, you know -
- because he's a friend of a friend -
- l helped him out, and look at this!
l mean -
You 're right, you 're right -
- l'll definitely take some action against him -
- some very strict action.
By the way, where's that package
you had to deliver?
Actually, l'm surprised it hasn't been delivered -
- l gave it to a friend - he's usually
very good at these things.
Something must have happened,
you know - we all are busy people.
Why don't you give me his address,
l mean, l'll have it picked up -
Are you sure?
No problem.
Where should l write, on my hand?
Yeah, sorry?
Yeah -
What's his name?
What the fuck?
Who's this?
Tashi.
So you 're Tashi?
Yeah, who the fuck are you ?
l ask the questions here -
- you calm down.
So you 're not Tashi?
No, sir. l told you -
- may l get down now?
Where's my package?
Package?
Enough, you fools.
A girl called Soniya gave you a package.
Where is it?
l don't know.
Really?
Ask the guy who dropped it off.
He isn't here.
Sisterfucker! What is this, a joke?
No, no, no, he's right -
- l dropped it off.
You dropped it off?
He's saying you 're not even here.
l think l'll just beat you guys a little more.
Sir, please listen to me -
- he gave it to someone to drop it off -
- and that guy, he gave it to me to -
Hang on, hang on -
You 're not Tashi -
- he is.
He got the package,
gave it to someone else -
- he gave it to you ,
and you dropped it off.
Yeah.
Then why didn't you say so?
Sir, you didn't ask.
Okay, l'm asking now.
Where is it?
l dropped it off at this place, shop -
lndian Handicrafts or something -
At lndian Handicrafts,
you dropped off a can of shit.
Where's my package?
No, sir. Shit?
Really?
Are you sure?
Am l sure?
Ask me again.
You 're probably right, you 're probably -
You 're absolutely right.
There must've been a mix up -
Mix-up?
Sisterfucker, l've had it with this -
lf l have to ask you one more time -
- l'm going to fucking kill you .
Package?
Doctor - it's at the doctor's office. Please.
Bunty.
Done?
Better?
Thank God you were there, otherwise -
Forget it, man.
Let's go.
Mr. NItIn?
Who is next?
Mr. Nitin.
Your friend dropped this off.
My friend? Why?
- Ready?
- Yeah.
What do you know about this guy?
Nothing. He's dead.
Sir, may l get down now?
l know he's dead.
But who did the flower arrangement?
Sir, if l could just get down,
l'll answer all your questions -
- my roommate took them.
Him?
No. My other roommate.
His photographer.
His photographer?
There's morons running around the city
photographing dead guys for him?
No sir, actually, he's a -
- journalist.
Thank you very much.
l really -
Forget it, man.
You 're like a stuck record.
You would've done
the same for me, right?
Right.
Okay. Got to go.
What happened -
- you 're not going home?
No, man -
- have to meet my brother.
You have a brother?
Hey, guys.
You must be the photojournalist.
Welcome. We've been waiting for you .
Where the hell were you ?
Park your ass over there.
Go.
First class.
Very good.
Finish them.
Wait a minute -
Finish them?
Why? You got everything
you want - no, no, no!
Arup!
Back off!
Hold him!
You fuckIng IdIot.!
Nobody can hear a thing in this racket.
l'll take it off -
You fuckhead, gimme that -
CarefuI -
- don't panIc.!
Go on, help her!
Don't worry, don't panIc.!
Arup!
Arup, come on, man!
Hurry, c'mon, get up!
Nitin, come on!
Wait, wait!
What're you doIng -
- come on, come on!
Stop! Stop!
ls this the tie l gave you ?
Yes.
Snacks are ready.!
Don't touch anything -
- God knows what diseases
you 're carrying.
What are you waiting for now, snacks?
No, l'll get going.
They shaved your head
before hanging you ?
No.
What?
So how come you 're bald?
l did.
You did?
What is this,
fucking Mill on the Floss?
What the hell just happened?
Where the fuck are we going?
Can we come in?
l'm sorry l picked them up -
- how can you just leave a bunch of
diamonds lying around?
I wasn't thInkIng -
- but now l am -
- l think let's just return them,
walk away from this whole thing.
We can't.
What, we'll just -
They tried to kill us
after they got them back.
What?
They trIed to kIII us
after they got them back -
- too late to walk away.
We can't just sell them and run,
l mean, where do we -
- sorry, aunty.
Where do we go?
Our lives are here.
Why can't we just go to the police?
Soniya will get into trouble.
She'll get into trouble?
This is all her fault -
- what the fuck has she been doing,
hanging out with fucking psychos?
PIease Ieave me a message
after the beep, bye.
And I know thIs Is your dowry, man,
but thIs Is an ugIy fuckIng ugIy car,
okay -
- when a donkey fucks a rIckshaw,
thIs Is what you get.
Three lakhs.
Three lakhs?
Final offer.
Okay.
Good, very good.
There's 30 diamonds here,
so the total is 90 lakhs.
Come back in half an hour -
- l'll have the cash.
Sorry, sorry - three lakhs each?
Three lakhs each.
See, now -
- this is my final offer -
- no bargaining.
Take it or leave it.
No, no, no -
- it's fine.
90 lakhs -
- it's okay.
I'II go to Patna -
- I'm gone fIve years, no,
I'II go to KashmIr -
- nobody will look there.
What are you doing?
l'm just, just checking.
Saw this movie once, cash on top,
and underneath they had stuffed
with all fucking newspaper -
- thIs Is, thIs Is aII cash -
- nIce guy, that Mr. AdIakha -
- where are you going to go?
Staying right here.
What?
They'II, they'II fInd you , man -
Yeah, they'll find me, they'll beat me,
and l'll tell them you 're in Patna.
Bastard.
Give me the phone.
Hello?
Bannerjee, you fucking hack!
You blot on every
Bong art director in the business!
I quIt.!
You talentless whore -
Talk.
Talk -
- talk!
By about 1 1 percent and -
- hello?
Bannerjee.
Hack!
You fucking hack!
Blot on every Bong
art director in the business!
What?
l quit, l quit!
l quit, you talentless whore -
God - godamnIt, who Is thIs?
lt's Arup, you dumb fuck -
- l quit!
Yeah?
TashI.!
I want them back. In one hour.
Room 50 7, HoteI Raj PaIace.
Or I'II send her back by parceI post.
What?
Who is it?
They've got Soniya.
They, who they?
We have to take the diamonds back -
- we have to return the money and
take the diamonds back.
What?
Take the money back?
l just quit my job -
- no, you 're right,
we have to do the right -
l - they didn't recognize me,
l can always tell them it wasn't - crap!
But we take the diamonds back,
they kill us.
Wasn't that the problem to begin with?
We don't have a choice.
We don't have a choice -
- what, we're just going to go back there
and get killed? That's the plan -
- to go back there and get -
Fuck, man, will you -
- shut the fuck up?
l hate your fucking girlfriend, man.
No problem.
Pay me back, take them.
They're yours, after all.
How much is this?
The 90 lakhs you gave us, all of it.
How many do you want to buy?
All of them.
That'll be double then.
Look, the 90 lakhs you gave us,
l'm giving it all back.
Please, just return our diamonds.
The guys who sold me the diamonds
had no idea of their value.
But l did. That's why double.
Look, l'm begging you -
- it's a matter of life and death.
My frIend -
- l've heard these sob stories before.
l'm running a business, not a charity.
Somebody will die, okay,
you understand?
We were here half-an-hour ago,
nothing has changed.
This is my final offer -
- double.
Tashi, no, no!
Throw him out!
Throw the motherfucking bastard out!
Where are we going?
Times of lndia.
For what?
l have a plan.
Drag me half-way across the city?
l only do that for people who know me -
- for friends, and in the middle
of the fucking day!
l have a deadline.
Trust me -
- so do l.
This is the plan?
Find a parking spot,
sit tight till we show up -
- simple as that.
Nothing to worry about -
- watch it!
Hey, aunty.!
Fuck off, you half-wit!
Can't see with this thing in my face!
Whatever you do,
keep your face covered.
l'm assuming there's going to be
an explanation at some point?
Yes, of course, but later.
Did you get the money?
Yeah.
Why do we have to give it back?
The guy's an asshole.
This isn't a robbery -
- we're taking back what's ours,
returning what's his.
Ours?
Nothing is ours -
- we're just the dumb fucks
stuck in the middle!
We should keep the fucking money -
Cow!
You drive, let me do the thinking.
Stop here, stop here.
Why here?
Because, I don't want to puII up
at the store In a brIght red car.
Okay, find a spot as close to the store
as you can, park there.
Man, l'm dying in this.
Do you know how hot this thing is?
Yes, l'm wearing one.
Move, you fuck -
are you blind?
No, not this either.
Ma'am , how about thIs one?
No, show me something else.
Ma'am , If you teII me
what you 're IookIng for,
I'II be abIe to heIp you better.
Not this, don't you have
anything else?
Okay, ma'am.
How about thIs?
Let's go!
Let's go, everything's crappy.
Hold on, hold on!
What's the matter, ma'am?
You didn't like anything?
No, this is garbage.
Why don't you step into my office?
l have something you 'll love.
Please, come.
Nafisa, will you wait here?
l'll be right back.
l'll be back.
Please, come.
Good afternoon.
How are you , sir?
Very well.
ls my set ready?
Or will you make me wait again?
Madam, orange juice?
Ladies first.
Thank you .
What range are you looking in?
Price is no object.
Only a connoisseur
can appreciate true craftsmanship.
Here you go. Just for you .
You won't find such fine work
anywhere else, l guarantee it.
Does it come with anklets?
Of course, let me show you .
Get back!
This isn't a robbery, l'm taking back
what's mine. Your money's outside.
You won't get away -
Don't worry about me, you thief.
Tape, tape.
Damn, fuck! You saala tevadia fucking rat,
fuck, l should rob you !
My sock!
Open your mouth!
Fuck!
Your set.
l never imagined it would
turn out so beautifully.
l want to thank him personally.
Where is he?
In hIs offIce, I'II caII hIm .
Walk, don't run.
Stop.!
Run, run, run!
Thank you .
Tashi, here!
Crazy -
- you guys!
Crazy!
What the f-
Menaka!
Shit, Menaka!
So, what was all this all about?
Save his wife.
She's not my wife.
Wife-to-be, fiance, whatever.
You 're engaged?
What was her name again?
Leena.
Once we're there, just point her out to me.
l'll take care of the rest.
l think we should just let them go
with a warning, right?
ls that what the whore-lover thinks?
l'll drag all those
godless bastards to the station -
- and thrash them senseless!
Control room, l'm following a red car,
request immediate backup!
Red car, DL 3C 6390, near Dhaula Kuan,
all units in area, please assist.
Sir?
Yeah, turn around.
Your boyfrIend was supposed to be
here by two. He Isn't here yet -
- personally, l have nothing against you -
- but l have no other choice.
Who knows what your story
would have been,
if you 'd fallen in love with someone else.
Please, please, please, l'm begging you ,
just five minutes, he'll be here.
Sorry, ma'am -
- deadline is a deadline.
1 0 -
What the -
Saw that?
Sir, can we try again?
You think?
We have ten minutes, we'll get bored.
Pick her up.
You guys wait here -
- l'll be back.
Okay.
l'm coming with you .
You don't have to -
- this is my problem.
l'm coming with you .
Man -
Will you wait here?
We'll be back soon.
l'll think about it.
Where are you going?
Where do you think?
8 -
- Please, please. No - no - no
- 7 -
6 -
5 -
4 -
- Please, l beg you -
- 3 -
Get it.
Hurry up, we don't have much time.
Give it to me.
Let her go first.
That was an order, not a request.
Man, don't fuck around.
First, the four of us
will go down to the lobby.
You come down, and l'll give it to you .
What are you doing, man?
ls that so?
Hurry up!
l'll tell you what'll happen.
First, l'll kill her -
- quIet.
Tashi, please give him what he wants -
Quiet.
Shut up!
What happened?
And then the three of you .
Either way, l'll get what l want.
You really think your bravery is
going to change the world?
You motherfucking -
Man, oh man.
Shit, shit -
Sisterfucker.
You 're pulling a gun on me?
Do you know how long
l've been in this business?
What do you think -
- putting a gun to my head gives you
permission to fuck me in the ass?
Sisterfucker!
Happy anniversary, darling -
- cheers.
Next time -
- can we please just go to -
- fucking Disneyland?
So, they are right -
- you are a lesbo.
l should've known.
What're you talking about, man?
l saw you , okay?
l saw you kissing that woman.
What're you doing,
following me around?
So won't deny it?
Rajeev, enough.!
So you 're not going to
deny it?
Stop, damn it -
Okay, who the hell were you kissing?
Who were you kissing?
Me.
She was kissing me -
- you don't approve?
She was kissing you ?
Fuck!
lt's well written.
Did you say it's brilliantly written?
l said, are you sure they can't
trace that fucking car back to us?
lt's in my father-in-law's name -
- he reported it stolen,
that should cover our asses.
He's not your father-in-law.
Yeah, yeah.
So, Soniya called off
the wedding?
No -
- l did.
You called it off?
He called it off?
So you don't mind if l ask
Soniya out to dinner, right?
Dude, what the -
What, she's hot man.
- You got more?
- Cupboard.
So, you called up that guy -
- art director, what's his name?
l'm done with that crap -
- l'm moving back home.
Why?
l can't make the
fucking rent, that's why.
Hey, what the heII -
what the heII Is thIs?
Don't look at me -
- it's the hand of God.
You crazy bastard.
What?
How can you do this?
You don't want It, I'II keep It aII -
Dude, don't touch It, don't, don't -
What are you doIng now?
Coming!
Stop your mischief.
Did you show daddy the card
you made for uncle?
Show it to him.
You made a card for uncle?
Very good -
- this is lovely
Read it to me.
Dear tauji, we are all very sorry -
- that bullet hit your bum.
We hope you can soon -
- go potty on your own.
ls that what you 've written?
He can't write that?
You 're right.
Actually beta, it should be -
- a bullet hit your bum.
We all are very sorry -
What are you doing?
You 'll break it!
Come on, let's go.
l don't have that car anymore.
The magic photo, this -
- it's yours.
No.
Goodbye, Tashi.
Sohaya with her latest single -
- l hate you , like l love you -
- like l love you , in brackets.
I hate you , IIke I Iove you ,
I hate you ,
like l love you ,
love you , love you !
Bastard -
- you 're goIng to pay for that.!
TheDarkMaster[TDM] -=MTR=-